# Marie Hooper

#### **EDUCATION**

B.S. Finance Entrepreneurship Minor University of Florida | 2011

#### INTERESTS

Wakeboarding Tennis Boating Traveling College Football

#### PROFILE

Enthusiastic and innovative professional with 3+ years of experience in business process analysis and design. Major strengths in relationship building, teamwork, user interface design and problem solving with a focus on customer service and attention to detail.

Business Process Design UI/UX Design HTML, CSS, JavaScript Google Apps Project Management









# EXPERIENCE

### AUG 2013 - PRESENT PROJECT MANAGEMENT ADMINISTRATOR | Wantman Group, Inc.

West Palm Beach, Florida

Helped president and project managers more accurately project revenue and staffing needs through proliferation of software

Assisted in design and development of company intranet and automation of multiple business processes

Spearheaded development of paperless contract management

Developed several applications to analyze financial metrics and track project pursuits

Performed all financial functions for transportation and civil engineering divisions

# MAY 2012 - JUL 2013 • BUSINESS SYSTEMS ANALYST | University of Michigan Athletic Dept.

Ann Arbor, Michigan

Designed and developed Athletic Department intranet for Athletic Department staff and student-athletes

Worked closely with project stakeholders to understand requirements for new applications and changes to existing ones

Managed a variety of projects and software selection/implementation through entire lifecycle

Interpreted and transformed end user needs into functional, intuitive solutions

Held monthly lunch and learn sessions to educate groups of 60+ staff about various technology applications

Automated multiple business processes throughout channels of Athletic department

Developed working knowledge of programming languages

Acted as a liaison between IT department, staff and outside software vendors

MAY 2012 - JUL 2013  $\blacklozenge$ 

#### **CERTIFIED PERSONAL TRAINER | Saline Fitness**

Saline, Michigan

Designed and implemented various circuit workouts for group boot camp fitness classes Motivated adults from a variety of fitness levels to create and achieve personal goals

Encouraged new member sign-ups through a variety of promotional activities

JAN 2012 - MAR 2012  $\phi$ 

# **OUTSIDE SALES DISTRICT MANAGER | ADP**

Los Angeles, California

Sold payroll, HR, employee benefit solutions to small businesses

Managed client relationships and lead generation from a variety of sales channels

# JUL 2009 - DEC 2011 FLOOR INSTRUCTOR/SUPERVISOR | Gainesville Health & Fitness

Gainesville, Florida

Helped members achieve fitness goals while building lasting relationships

Responsible for training and testing potential and new employees

Promotion to shift Supervisor, responsible for 6 employees in various departments and facilities